

VLADIMIR GORLOV

IT PROJECT MANAGER

ABOUT ME

Certified IT project manager,
PhD in Science (Math and Physics), Associate Professor with
more than 12 years of experience and extensive knowledge,
skills and abilities in the field
of higher mathematics, physics,
modeling of various processes,
telecommunication systems and
networks, marketing,
data analytics, project
management.
Managed the development of 16

Managed the development of 16 graduation projects, 2 R&D projects and 23 software products in the field of advanced and breakthrough network protocols based on self-organizing and self-configuring networks and queuing systems using Agile methodology using Scrum, Kanban, TDD, BDD, MDD.

CONTACTS

Voronezh Phone: +7-915-541-11-15 Email: gorlov.vladimir@gmail.com

> PORTFOLIO CERTIFICATES

https://github.com/VLADI-MIR-G84/Projects_public

Certipro. Certification

Scrum Foundation
Professional Certificate SFPC™ by CertiProf

EDUCATION

- 2022 Software Product Management Specialization, University of Alberta, Coursera
- 2022 Google Project Management: Professional Certificate, Google, Coursera
- 2022 Google Data Analytics: Professional Certificate, Google, Coursera
- 2018 VUNC "Air Force Academy named after Professor N.E. Zhukovsky and Yu.A. Gagarin" (Voronezh). Academic rank: Associate Professor. Specialization: 01.01.02 Differential equations, dynamical systems and optimal control.
- 2016–2017 Institute of Management, Marketing and Finance, RIMA-B (INHOLLAND University, the Netherlands and State University of Management).
 Diploma (Immif), Diploma (RIMA-GUU and INHOLLAND), international certificate in marketing (INHOLLAND and NUFFIC). Specialization: Strategic and international marketing.
- ➤ 2008–2012 Voronezh State University. Faculty of Mathematics. Department of Mathematical Modeling.

 Academic degree: PhD in Science (Math and Physics). Specialization: 01.01.02 Differential equations, dynamical systems and optimal control.
- 2010–2011 Institute of Management, Marketing and Finance, RIMA-A (INHOLLAND University, the Netherlands and State University of Management).
 Diploma (Immif), Diploma (RIMA-GUU and INHOLLAND), international certificate in marketing (INHOLLAND and NUFFIC). Specialization: Operational marketing.
- ➤ 2008-2011 Voronezh State University. Faculty of Mathematics. Department of Mathematical Modeling.
 Postgraduate program. Specialization: 01.01.02 Differential equations, dynamical systems and optimal control.
- 2005-2008 Voronezh State University. Faculty of Romance and Germanic Philology. Specialty: Interpreter in the field of professional communication. Average score: 5.0
- 2006-2008 Voronezh State University. Faculty of Mathematics. Department of Mathematical Modeling.
 Master's Degree in Mathematics. Diploma topic: "Model of economic growth with regard to the influence of intellectual labor. The case of a three-sector economy." Average score: 4.8
- 2002-2006 Voronezh State University. Faculty of Mathematics. Department of Mathematical Modeling.
 Bachelor's Degree in Mathematics. Diploma topic: "Model of economic growth with regard to the influence of intellectual labor" Average score: 4.6
- ➤ 1999-2002 Natural-technical college of the Voronezh State Technical University. Specialty: Management (engineering industry). Average score: 5.0

PERSONAL **SKILLS**

- Detail-oriented
- Responsibility
- Management skills
- Communication skills
 - Critical thinking
- High ability to learning
 - Analytical skills
 - Interpersonal skills
 - OKRs Focus
 - Problem Solving
 - Decision Making
 - Multitasking
 - Leadership skills
 - Creativity

PROGRAMMING. **PROGRAMS**

Languages: Python, R, XML, SQL, HTML, MATLAB

OS:

MS Windows, Mac OS, Linux using command line, VM Oracle

Modeling:

AnyLogic, Mathematica, NS-3, Cisco Racket Tracer, NetSim, NetCracker, Simulink

Programs:

Miro, Asana, Trello, Git, Jira, OpenProject, Github, Tableau, Power BI, MS Office software (MS Word, Excel, Access, PowerPoint, Visio, Project, Publisher), LaTeX, etc.

PROJECT MANAGEMENT

Process models: Waterfall model, V-model, Sawtooth model, Spiral model, UPM, Prototypes model, continuous delivery model, Microsoft Daily Build, Agile model Agile Practices:

Scrum, Extreme Programming, Pair Programming, Lean Six Sigma: Lean Software Design, Kanban, Devops, CI/CD, SAFe, LeSS,

"10-to-3-to-1" Apple model, "Design Sprint" Google model, "Design Thinking" IBM model, Spotify model, TDD, BDD, MDD

EXPERIENCE

> 07.2021 - 03.2022 "National Research University "Moscow Institute of Electronic Technology" (MIET). Advanced Research Foundation - Laboratory of Breakthrough Radio Communication Technologies (Moscow)

Lead Engineer TBL (Targeted Breakthrough Laboratory) MIET

1. Managed, planned, implemented and supervised projects in accordance with the Agile methodology and methodologies of TDD, BDD and MDD in the field of advanced network technologies in telecommunication

systems. 23 software products have been developed and implemented.

2. Managed project backlogs, planned project sprints in accordance with Scrum, managed sprint execution using Kanban.

3. Risk management and project budgeting.

4. Modeled telecommunication systems and network protocols based on self-organizing and self-configuring networks in MATLAB, NS-3, Python.

5. Prepared scientific and technical reports, reports and presentations for the management of the Fund on the process of project execution and closure, as well as scientific publications on the researches and developed technologies. oped technologies.

08.2015 – 07.2021 VUNC "Air Force Academy named after Professor N.E. Zhukovsky and Yu. A. Gagarin" (Voronezh)

Associate Professor of the Department of Communications (and Aviation Communications Complexes)

1. Conducted all types of classes in the disciplines "Information transmission networks", "Fundamentals of the theory of radio information transmission systems", "Optical devices", "Optico-electronic devices".

2. Prepared and developed educational and methodological materials of disciplines, supervised the process of correct use of educational and

disciplines, supervised the process of correct use of educational and methodological materials.

3. Planned, controlled the entire range of responsibilities for the methodological activities of the department and accounting for the control of training sessions: planning the annual plan, timely making changes to the activity plan; preparing, organizing and holding conferences, meetings, seminars, round tables at the department and faculty; preparing intermediate and final reports on the methodological activities of the department; summarizing the activities of the department in accordance with the Project Retrospective and the development of methods for improving activities. For 4 years was The Best Methodologist of the department.

4. Supervised and managed in accordance with Scrum and Kanban 16 graduation projects and 2 R&D in the field of modern information transmission networks, dynamic systems, optimal control and queuing systems.

5. Research activity on the study of equations of mathematical physics, optimal control, dynamic systems, radio systems, queuing systems, as well as on the study of advanced information transmission systems. 3 years The Best (first place) in terms of publication activity in the ranking of scientific work of departments, Research Center, Research and Development Department of VUNC "Air Force Academy".

6. Performed the duties of the Chairman of the SMC (subject-methodical commission) of the department; planning control summarizing the ac-

commission) of the department: planning, control, summarizing the activities of the SMC of the department in accordance with Project Retrospective, organizing meetings, keeping minutes of meetings and preparing extracts from the minutes of meetings of the SMC, developing methods for improving activities.

> 09.2013 - 08.2015 VUNC "Air Force Academy named after Professor N.E. Zhukovsky and Yu. A. Gagarin" (Voronezh)

Lecturer at the Department of Mathematics

1. Conducted all types of classes in the disciplines "Mathematics", "Mathematical Analysis", "Fundamentals of Probability Theory and Mathematical Statistics", "Analytic Geometry and Linear Algebra", "Informatics".
2. Prepared and developed educational and methodological materials

for disciplines.

3. Research activities in the study of the equations of mathematical physics, optimal control, dynamic systems, as well as applied problems in the study of radio systems and signals.
4. Supervised the military-scientific work of cadets.

FOREIGN LANGUAGES

English language: - Proficiency (CERF). EFSET Certificate

German: B1 - Intermediate (CERF). Level test result.

INTERESTS

Information technologies

Management

Marketing

Foreign languages

Volleyball

Running

Science

ACHIEVEMENTS

- ✓ Lead and developer of 30 tutorials and e-learning programs on information networks, in particular on wireless networks, cellular networks, 4G mobile networks and optimal management.
- ✓ Author of about 80 scientific publications of articles, including those added in the international citation databases Scopus and Web of science.
- ✓ 2018, 2019, 2020, 2021 The Best Methodologist of the department and faculty at VUNC "Air Force Academy ".
- √ 2018, 2019, 2020 The best (first place) in terms of publication activity in the rating of scientific work of the departments, Research Center, Research and Development Center of the Air Force Academy.
- ✓ Course <u>certificate</u> "Innovation Management". Erasmus University. Rotterdam.
- Certificates of preparation courses for certification CAPM, PMI-ACP.

EXPERIENCE

> 7.2011 - 9.2011 OGU "Agency for Innovation and Development" (Voronezh)

Chief Development Officer

1. Managed three innovative projects: the creation of a recreational park in the Voronezh region; a plant for rolling basalt pipes; and a project for waste-free fish processing.

2. Making changes to updating information on the corporate website.

3. Preparation of reports on the process of project execution.

01.2010 - 06.2010 Voronezh State University (Voronezh)

Lecturer at the Department of Mathematical Modeling

1. Conducted all types of classes in the disciplines "Mathematical and economic models in economics" and "Mathematical methods in eco-

2. Prepared and developed educational and methodological materials

for disciplines.

3. Research activities in the study of the equations of mathematical physics, optimal control, dynamic systems, as well as applied problems in the study of radio systems and signals.

4. Supervised the scientific work of students.

05.2008 – 06.2009 JSC "Yabloko" (Voronezh)

Marketing Assistant

Conducted product market analysis.

Conducted analytical (desk) research.

3. Collected and analyzed statistical information;
4. Conducted qualitative and quantitative marketing research;
5. Prepared analytical reports on the company's activities and predicted'sales volume.

09.2007 – 05.2008 ISC "Yabloko" (Voronezh)

Financial Analyst Assistant

Economic modeling; analysis of business processes in order to optimize; data collection and processing; participation in the analysis of the financial and economic activities of the enterprise; formation of analytical reports; maintenance of operational databases; work with various sources of information

06.2005 – 08.2005 Voronezh State University (Voronezh)

PC operator, admissions officer

Advising applicants and their parents for admission to the university checking documents, accepting electronic applications, providing additional information about faculties and specialties.